AMANDA CLAIRE: All right, so already we've saved a lot of money.
I mean, the embroidery hoops are cheap, this fabric like this can be, you know, sometimes 50 cents a yard.
I mean, that's about what I paid for this like 50, 75 cents a yard; very, very cheap stuff.
And so we've already saved a lot of money with that.
We don't have to buy any emulsion.
One thing you really can't, you know be miserly about, you know, something you really do kinda need to be spending some money on are the correct kinds of paint or ink for screen printing.
And you don't want to just use any old paint or any old ink.
You really want to kinda go to an art store or to a printing store and get the right stuff and so if you're going to be printing onto paper, there's certain inks you would use for that.
If you're going to be printing on the fabric, there's certain inks that you would use for that.
So I have some of them here, some fabric screen printing ink; these are by the Speedball company, but I'm not endorsing them, I'm just saying that, from the Speedball company; there's different companies that sell this stuff.
You know, yellow--I have a few colors here, yellow, red, white.
You can even mix these colors if you want to kind of make your own colors.
So these are your screen printing inks, but just remember when you go shopping for inks, you know get the colors you want and you know, shop around a bit.
You know buy these from a printing or craft supply store, but remember you do need a different type of ink depending on what kind of printing your doing.
So these actually say fabric inks on them, fabric screen printing ink, so these are good for printing t-shirts.
But if I was going to print posters or you know any kind of art print or I don't know, greeting cards or something, I would want to get a different kind of ink that's used for that.